oh my gosh I was so wrong is this one of
those things I could have just looked
up maybe I don't know but I don't care
because I found it and now my wonderful
Bonsai project can be used by everyone
Zell and Bash users
alike I'm sorry fish and Powershell we
haven't got you yet we'll get you check
this out check this out my friends this
is an official project
before we found this we actually CH one
of our community members actually found
recreated the exact same script which
already existed in the zshell project so
under the github.com Zell users zsh here
you'll see a directory called completion
and there is this really amazing script
called bash comp and knit and if you run
this if you put this in your zshell
which you know I don't know how to do
because I don't use zshell use bash
guess what you can use bash completion
so you can use complete- cfu Fu and you
can actually let the programs do their
own completion not only that but if you
want to use bash completion in other
ways so say you're having like Cobra
completion or something like that you
can use it you can use bash completion
100% in Zell and there's going to be at
least one comment from someone and I
will upot you and pin you if you say so
he's like yeah no duh dummy well don't
say dummy but you know you know but if
you don't know about this go use this
right now this makes me very happy this
means there's nothing about Bonsai that
can't be used by the two most biggest
shells